Preliminary Guide to the Rufus Lusk & Sons business and personal records, 1896-1994 MS2189
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Business records, 1930-1994; Series 1
  - Real estate business records, 1930-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Correspondence, Circa 1940, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - American Security and Trust Co. special job, proposed Blair Road Branch, 1962; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Lusk photograph reproduction project, 1940-1966, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Certificate of Incorporation Rufus S. Lusk and Son Inc., 1957; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Silver Jubilee, 1955; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Lusk Co. Stock, 1986-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Financial reports, 1987-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - A case study on the impact of real estate deed information on public policy (washington post articles), 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - REI News, Winter 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Washington Times, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Ledger book related to directories, 1964-1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Financial records, 1948-1991; Series 1 Subseries 3
    For ease of browsing the files with financial records have been intellectually grouped together in this subseries. The files in this subseries are arranged in original order by box number.
    - Budget, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1981-1991; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Financial Reports [1/2], 1983-1990; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Financial Reports [2/2], 1978-1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Report of Audit, 1951 December 31; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports, 1952 December 31 - 1955 December 31; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Financial Reports, 1955 March 31 - 1957 December 31; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Financial Reports, 1958 March 31 - 1959 December 31; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Financial Reports, 1961-1964; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Financial Reports, 1970-1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Financial Statements, 1961-1973; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Record of check disbursed, 1959; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Payroll records, 1959; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 5, Box R1, Folder 7)
      This file is closed for 100 years to date of record creation.
    - Record of check disbursed, 1960; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Payroll records, 1960; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 8, Box 36, Folder 7)
    - General ledger, 1956-1957; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - General ledger, 1964; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - General ledger, 1965; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - General Journal, 1952-1962; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Payroll records, 1945; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 1, Box 37, Folder 2)
    - General ledger, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Payroll records, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 4, Box R1, Folder 2)
    - General ledger, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Payroll records, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 3, Box 37, Folder 6)
    - General ledger, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Payroll records, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 4, Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Record of check disbursed, 1953; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Payroll records, 1953; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box R1, Folder 5, Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Record of check disbursed, 1957; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Payroll records, 1957; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 12, Box R1, Folder 6)
    - General ledger, 1960-1961; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Corporation savings and loan pass books, undated; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1958-1959; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1960-1961; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1962; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1963; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1964; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1965; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1967; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1968; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1969; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1971; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1972; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1973; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1974; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Corporation tax returns, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Corporate tax returns and financial statements, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Income tax returns [corporate], 1985; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Tax returns [corporate], 1986; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Tax returns [corporate], 1987; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1948-1951; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1949-1954; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1955-1958; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1959-1960; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1961; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1962; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1963-1964; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1965-1968; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1969-1971; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1972-1976; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1977-1980; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Corporation financial reports, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. correspondence - general, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. catalog requests, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc Correspondence Re Inquiries, 1952-1953; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. Correspondence, Re Inquiries, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. Inquiries, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. invoices paid, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. invoices paid, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. orders and confirmations, 1952; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. orders and confirmations, 1951; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - W.S. Ponton, Inc. orders and confirmations, 1950; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Financial statements for the twelve month period ending 12/31/1991, Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Payroll ledger, 1964-1968; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Sales receipt ledger, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Financial statements, 1952-1961 June 30; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Account ledger [receivable, sales], 1963; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Cash receipt book, 1966; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Civic and personal records, 1896-1971; Series 2
  Organized into 3 subseries: Gourmet Society Dinner club, Washington Taxpayers' Association (WTA) and the Washington Taxpayers' Protective Association (WTPA) and Personal papers.
  - Gourmet Society Dinner Club, 1947-1971; Series 2 Subseries 1
    For ease of browsing the files related to the Gourmet Society Dinner Club have been intellectually grouped together in this subseries. The files in this subseries are arranged in original order by box number.
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1947; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1948; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1952; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1953; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1954; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1955; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Gourmet - Menus [Gourmet Society], 1956; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Gourmet Dinner [Gourmet Society], 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Gourmet Dinner [Gourmet Society], 1958; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Gourmet Dinner [Gourmet Society], 1959; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Gourmet Dinner [Gourmet Society], 1960; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Gourmet Dinner [Gourmet Society], 1961; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Gourmet Dinners [Gourmet Society], 1962; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Gourmet Dinners [Gourmet Society], 1963; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Gourmet Society dinner menus, 1964; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Gourmet Society dinner menus, 1965; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Gourmet Society dinner menus, 1966; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Gourmet Society dinner menus, 1967; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Gourmet Society - miscellaneous, 1949; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Gourmet correspondence [Gourmet Society], 1950-1954; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Gourmet correspondence [Gourmet Society], 1955-1957; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Gourmet correspondence [Gourmet Society], 1958-1959; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Gourmet correspondence [Gourmet Society], 1960-1961; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Gourmet correspondence [Gourmet Society], 1962-1968; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Gourmet Society list of members, 1961; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Bank statements [Gourmet Society], 1969; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Gourmet dinner attendence [Gourmet Society], 1950-1960; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Gourmet dinner attendence [Gourmet Society], 1961; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Gourmet dinner hosts [Gourmet Society], 1947-1965; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Gourmet literature etc., 1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Gourmet quotations for future use? [Gourmet Society], 1948-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Gourmet's guide to Washington [Gourmet Society], 1943-1951; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Gourmet Society publicity, 1949-1950; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Gourmet Society - wine catalogues, recipes, etc., undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1961 May 16; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1961 October 23; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1962 January 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1963 June 19; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1963 April 24; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1964 April 21; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1964 November - December; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1965 January 28; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1965 March 3; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1966 January 20; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1967 April 18; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Gourmet Society dinner, 1967 May 19; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Gourmet Society financial, Circa 1970-1971; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Gourmet Society Dinner, 1949, 1961; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Washington Taxpayers' Association (WTA) and Washington Taxpayers' Protective Association (WTPA), 1933-1959; Series 2 Subseries 2
    For ease of browsing the files with related to the WTA and WTPA are intellectually grouped together in this subseries. The files in this subseries are arranged in box number order to leave some understanding of how these were originally grouped together.
    When applicable the folders that are known to have Washington Taxpayer's Association materials, but not identified in the title staff added [WTA] to the title. Also, when applicable the folders known to have Washington Taxpayer's Protective Association, but not identified in the title staff added [WPTA] to the title.
    - Washington Taxpayers Protective Association, 1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Baltimore Md. Association, 1931-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - American Liberty League, 1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - American Taxpayers League, Inc., 1933-1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - A 1934 [correspondence], Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - E.C. Baltz, chairman of the Board [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Bank statement [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Bill on interest for cash balances, Circa 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Board of Trade [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - B [correspondence], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Taxpayer's League clippings, undated; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Congressional correspondence, 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Congressional correspondence, 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Commission correspondence [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Commission correspondence [WTPA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Letters - to contributors and from contributors [WTPA], 1935 June - December; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Letters - to contributors and from contributors [WTPA], 1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Contributions [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Contribution form letters [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Contribution form letters [WTPA], 1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Contribution form letters [WTPA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Bank statement [WTPA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - C-E [correspondence, WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee [WTPA], 1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - F-I [correspondence, WTPA], 1934-1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Instate Bond Company Atlanta, Ga Geo. P. Street, Pres [WTPA], 1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - J-M [correspondence, [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - David B. Karrick, 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Letters from contributors [WTPA], 1934-1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Membership [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Membership [WTPA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Mimeographed bulletins [WTA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Mimeographed bulletins [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Mimeographed letters and statements [WTPA], 1933; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Mimeographed letters and statements [WTPA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Minutes [WTPA], 1933; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Mr. Lusk correspondence [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Mailing list [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Washington Taxpayers Protective Association, 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Washington Taxpayers Protective Association, 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Monthly financial statements [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Monthly financial statements [WTPA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Municipal finance newsletter, 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - news releases [WTPA], 1934-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Organization Committee for the Formation of a Taxpayer League in the District of Columbia, 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Taxpayer Association organization materials, 1933; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - New York City Association, 1933; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Philadephia, Pa., 1933; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Letters to prospective members [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - P.W.A. requirements, 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - P.W.A. ballot [WTPA], undated; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - P-R [correspondence, WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Receipts [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Receipts [WTPA], 1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Receipts [WTPA], 1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Rough draft material, Circa 1931-1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - James McD. Shea, Treas., 1933-1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Statistics, 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - S [correspondence, [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Tax cut S-3404, 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Taxpayer Union, 1932-1933; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Tax Policy League, 1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - T-V [correspondence, [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - weekly financial statements [WTPA], 1933-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - weekly financial statements [WTPA], 1935-1936; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - W-Z [correspondence, [WTPA], 1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Taxpayers Association statistics and reports, 1930-1934; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - [empty mailing envelopes for WTPA indicating payment] [1/2], 1934-1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - [empty mailing envelopes for WTPA indicating payment] [2/2], 1934-1935; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - [related to the use of gasoline tax, postcards from the WTPA], 1934 April; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - A [WTA], 1942-1949; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Accounts payable [WTA], 1946-1952; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - B [WTA], 1940-1950; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Baltz, E.C. Chairman of the Board [WTA], 1940-1946; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Bank statements [WTA], 1950-1954; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Bank statements [WTA], 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Benefits for veterans of world wars No. 1 and 2 GI Bill of Rights [WTA], 1944; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors [WTPA], 1949; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trade, Washington [WTA], 1949; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of the budget [WTA], 1940; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - D.C. Budget [WTA], 1951-1949; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Budget worksheets M.R.C. [WTA], 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - C [WTA], 1941-1950; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America [WTA], 1942-1944; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Citizens associations [WTA], 1940; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Citizens National Committee [WTA], 1944; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - City Finances individual city reports, Bureau of the Census, Dept. of Commerce [WTA], 1944; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Civic Federation and Bureau of Public Efficiency [WTA], 1942-1948; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Commissioners, D.C. Board of Correspondence [WTA], 1949; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Commissioners, D.C. Board of Correspondence [WTA], 1950-1951; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Commissioners' Tax Committee [WTA], 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Committee on Municipal Assembly [WTA], 1941; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Congressional correspondence [WTA], 1950; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - D [WTA], 1940-1949; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Day Care bill for children [WTA], 1946; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Dinner meeting - executive committee and district officials [WTA], 1949 November 9; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Dinner meeting - executive committee and district officials [WTA], 1953 April 29; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Dinner meeting - executive committee and district officials [WTA], 1954 February 10; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Dinner meeting - executive committee and district officials [WTA], 1955 February 9; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 83, Folder 29)
    - Dinner Acceptances [WTA], 1959 December 2; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Dinner meeting - district officials WTA executive committee and members, 1959 December 2; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - D.C. tax program, suggested (Answer to letter sent to WTA members), 1946-1947; Series 2 Subseries2 (Box 84, Folder 3)